{"Question": "5 + 0 * 1 =", "Answer": 5, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "8 + 8 * 2 =", "Answer": 24, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "0 + 8 * 9 =", "Answer": 72, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "6 + 3 * 6 =", "Answer": 24, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "5 + 8 * 6 =", "Answer": 53, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "0 + 1 * 2 =", "Answer": 2, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 3 * 5 =", "Answer": 24, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "0 + 0 * 6 =", "Answer": 0, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "5 + 9 * 7 =", "Answer": 68, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "3 + 7 * 4 =", "Answer": 31, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "5 + 4 * 6 =", "Answer": 29, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "5 + 3 * 0 =", "Answer": 5, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "5 + 2 * 3 =", "Answer": 11, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 4 * 5 =", "Answer": 22, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "4 + 3 * 2 =", "Answer": 10, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 6 * 5 =", "Answer": 32, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 4 * 6 =", "Answer": 26, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "5 + 8 * 9 =", "Answer": 77, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "5 + 4 * 8 =", "Answer": 37, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "7 + 8 * 8 =", "Answer": 71, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "0 + 7 * 6 =", "Answer": 42, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 3 * 9 =", "Answer": 36, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 4 * 1 =", "Answer": 13, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "7 + 0 * 9 =", "Answer": 7, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "5 + 2 * 5 =", "Answer": 15, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "7 + 8 * 7 =", "Answer": 63, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 1 * 5 =", "Answer": 14, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "3 + 5 * 0 =", "Answer": 3, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 0 * 0 =", "Answer": 2, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "0 + 3 * 6 =", "Answer": 18, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "8 + 1 * 9 =", "Answer": 17, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 3 * 2 =", "Answer": 8, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "7 + 1 * 8 =", "Answer": 15, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "4 + 0 * 6 =", "Answer": 4, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "7 + 9 * 7 =", "Answer": 70, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 1 * 7 =", "Answer": 16, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "0 + 6 * 4 =", "Answer": 24, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 6 * 5 =", "Answer": 39, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "8 + 9 * 0 =", "Answer": 8, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "3 + 8 * 3 =", "Answer": 27, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "3 + 7 * 5 =", "Answer": 38, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 4 * 4 =", "Answer": 25, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "7 + 4 * 7 =", "Answer": 35, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "6 + 2 * 6 =", "Answer": 18, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "5 + 6 * 0 =", "Answer": 5, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "1 + 0 * 0 =", "Answer": 1, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 3 * 2 =", "Answer": 15, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "7 + 5 * 8 =", "Answer": 47, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "7 + 0 * 8 =", "Answer": 7, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "8 + 3 * 4 =", "Answer": 20, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "3 + 3 * 9 =", "Answer": 30, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 9 * 3 =", "Answer": 36, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 5 * 5 =", "Answer": 34, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "6 + 2 * 8 =", "Answer": 22, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "6 + 3 * 7 =", "Answer": 27, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "0 + 1 * 0 =", "Answer": 0, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 1 * 9 =", "Answer": 11, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "1 + 9 * 0 =", "Answer": 1, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "8 + 3 * 5 =", "Answer": 23, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "8 + 5 * 8 =", "Answer": 48, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 4 * 3 =", "Answer": 14, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 7 * 0 =", "Answer": 2, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "1 + 1 * 5 =", "Answer": 6, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "7 + 0 * 3 =", "Answer": 7, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "0 + 1 * 6 =", "Answer": 6, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "1 + 3 * 3 =", "Answer": 10, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "4 + 0 * 1 =", "Answer": 4, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "7 + 9 * 9 =", "Answer": 88, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "8 + 9 * 3 =", "Answer": 35, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "1 + 8 * 9 =", "Answer": 73, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 9 * 0 =", "Answer": 9, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "0 + 6 * 5 =", "Answer": 30, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "7 + 0 * 2 =", "Answer": 7, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "6 + 4 * 0 =", "Answer": 6, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "0 + 7 * 0 =", "Answer": 0, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "8 + 1 * 6 =", "Answer": 14, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "6 + 0 * 2 =", "Answer": 6, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "8 + 7 * 7 =", "Answer": 57, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 7 * 9 =", "Answer": 72, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "3 + 5 * 4 =", "Answer": 23, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "5 + 9 * 6 =", "Answer": 59, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 2 * 8 =", "Answer": 18, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "4 + 0 * 8 =", "Answer": 4, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 3 * 1 =", "Answer": 5, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 6 * 6 =", "Answer": 45, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "3 + 3 * 0 =", "Answer": 3, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "3 + 2 * 3 =", "Answer": 9, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 9 * 2 =", "Answer": 27, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 2 * 0 =", "Answer": 2, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "3 + 1 * 1 =", "Answer": 4, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "5 + 6 * 9 =", "Answer": 59, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 7 * 8 =", "Answer": 65, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "3 + 6 * 9 =", "Answer": 57, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "3 + 8 * 4 =", "Answer": 35, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "1 + 7 * 2 =", "Answer": 15, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "4 + 3 * 3 =", "Answer": 13, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "7 + 3 * 3 =", "Answer": 16, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 4 * 7 =", "Answer": 37, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "6 + 6 * 5 =", "Answer": 36, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 3 * 6 =", "Answer": 27, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "3 + 7 * 2 =", "Answer": 17, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "8 + 5 * 3 =", "Answer": 23, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "1 + 1 * 3 =", "Answer": 4, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "7 + 6 * 9 =", "Answer": 61, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "7 + 8 * 1 =", "Answer": 15, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 5 * 8 =", "Answer": 42, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "1 + 3 * 1 =", "Answer": 4, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "5 + 2 * 1 =", "Answer": 7, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 3 * 4 =", "Answer": 21, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "4 + 8 * 9 =", "Answer": 76, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "3 + 5 * 9 =", "Answer": 48, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "1 + 2 * 0 =", "Answer": 1, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 0 * 2 =", "Answer": 2, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 3 * 8 =", "Answer": 26, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 9 * 0 =", "Answer": 2, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "5 + 2 * 2 =", "Answer": 9, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "7 + 5 * 2 =", "Answer": 17, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 0 * 0 =", "Answer": 9, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "1 + 6 * 7 =", "Answer": 43, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "6 + 1 * 1 =", "Answer": 7, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "7 + 6 * 5 =", "Answer": 37, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "4 + 2 * 3 =", "Answer": 10, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 9 * 7 =", "Answer": 65, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "1 + 2 * 6 =", "Answer": 13, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "7 + 2 * 5 =", "Answer": 17, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 7 * 6 =", "Answer": 51, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "0 + 0 * 5 =", "Answer": 0, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "4 + 8 * 5 =", "Answer": 44, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "1 + 1 * 2 =", "Answer": 3, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 9 * 3 =", "Answer": 29, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 0 * 2 =", "Answer": 9, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 3 * 4 =", "Answer": 14, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "1 + 8 * 4 =", "Answer": 33, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 1 * 3 =", "Answer": 12, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "6 + 7 * 3 =", "Answer": 27, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "4 + 2 * 7 =", "Answer": 18, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 2 * 3 =", "Answer": 15, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "5 + 9 * 0 =", "Answer": 5, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 3 * 7 =", "Answer": 23, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "8 + 7 * 3 =", "Answer": 29, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "4 + 8 * 8 =", "Answer": 68, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "8 + 9 * 1 =", "Answer": 17, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "8 + 5 * 9 =", "Answer": 53, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "6 + 2 * 1 =", "Answer": 8, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "4 + 1 * 3 =", "Answer": 7, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 4 * 7 =", "Answer": 30, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "7 + 8 * 6 =", "Answer": 55, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "5 + 6 * 6 =", "Answer": 41, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "8 + 6 * 7 =", "Answer": 50, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "3 + 0 * 9 =", "Answer": 3, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "4 + 9 * 5 =", "Answer": 49, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "4 + 4 * 3 =", "Answer": 16, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "6 + 7 * 5 =", "Answer": 41, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "6 + 4 * 5 =", "Answer": 26, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "6 + 1 * 2 =", "Answer": 8, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "0 + 5 * 5 =", "Answer": 25, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 4 * 0 =", "Answer": 2, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "5 + 8 * 1 =", "Answer": 13, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 3 * 3 =", "Answer": 11, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "1 + 8 * 0 =", "Answer": 1, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "4 + 9 * 9 =", "Answer": 85, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 3 * 3 =", "Answer": 18, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 8 * 3 =", "Answer": 26, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "0 + 8 * 1 =", "Answer": 8, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "7 + 1 * 0 =", "Answer": 7, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "5 + 9 * 1 =", "Answer": 14, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "8 + 8 * 6 =", "Answer": 56, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "4 + 0 * 0 =", "Answer": 4, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "5 + 5 * 2 =", "Answer": 15, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "1 + 4 * 4 =", "Answer": 17, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "6 + 2 * 3 =", "Answer": 12, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "5 + 5 * 9 =", "Answer": 50, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "1 + 7 * 8 =", "Answer": 57, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 4 * 3 =", "Answer": 21, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "0 + 3 * 2 =", "Answer": 6, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "5 + 7 * 8 =", "Answer": 61, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 2 * 2 =", "Answer": 13, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "4 + 3 * 6 =", "Answer": 22, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "4 + 8 * 0 =", "Answer": 4, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 5 * 1 =", "Answer": 7, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "4 + 4 * 2 =", "Answer": 12, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "7 + 9 * 8 =", "Answer": 79, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "6 + 6 * 2 =", "Answer": 18, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 5 * 0 =", "Answer": 2, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "6 + 3 * 1 =", "Answer": 9, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 7 * 1 =", "Answer": 16, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "5 + 8 * 7 =", "Answer": 61, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "1 + 6 * 4 =", "Answer": 25, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 1 * 4 =", "Answer": 6, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "0 + 8 * 3 =", "Answer": 24, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "1 + 2 * 5 =", "Answer": 11, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "1 + 3 * 2 =", "Answer": 7, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "0 + 9 * 2 =", "Answer": 18, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "7 + 4 * 5 =", "Answer": 27, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "0 + 2 * 3 =", "Answer": 6, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "5 + 4 * 2 =", "Answer": 13, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "0 + 3 * 9 =", "Answer": 27, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "8 + 6 * 1 =", "Answer": 14, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "0 + 2 * 8 =", "Answer": 16, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 9 * 1 =", "Answer": 18, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "8 + 7 * 0 =", "Answer": 8, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "4 + 2 * 1 =", "Answer": 6, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "7 + 2 * 0 =", "Answer": 7, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 2 * 9 =", "Answer": 20, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "6 + 8 * 6 =", "Answer": 54, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "4 + 1 * 6 =", "Answer": 10, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "4 + 2 * 0 =", "Answer": 4, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "3 + 1 * 3 =", "Answer": 6, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "7 + 6 * 4 =", "Answer": 31, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "8 + 6 * 2 =", "Answer": 20, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "1 + 3 * 6 =", "Answer": 19, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "0 + 7 * 2 =", "Answer": 14, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 5 * 7 =", "Answer": 37, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "1 + 2 * 1 =", "Answer": 3, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 7 * 3 =", "Answer": 30, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "6 + 9 * 4 =", "Answer": 42, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "0 + 5 * 3 =", "Answer": 15, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "4 + 4 * 6 =", "Answer": 28, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "5 + 6 * 7 =", "Answer": 47, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "8 + 5 * 2 =", "Answer": 18, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "1 + 4 * 3 =", "Answer": 13, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "1 + 1 * 9 =", "Answer": 10, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "1 + 6 * 6 =", "Answer": 37, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "6 + 0 * 8 =", "Answer": 6, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "4 + 3 * 0 =", "Answer": 4, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "3 + 3 * 5 =", "Answer": 18, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "0 + 0 * 8 =", "Answer": 0, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "6 + 2 * 9 =", "Answer": 24, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "3 + 5 * 2 =", "Answer": 13, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "3 + 9 * 0 =", "Answer": 3, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 2 * 4 =", "Answer": 17, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "0 + 3 * 8 =", "Answer": 24, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 9 * 1 =", "Answer": 11, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 3 * 8 =", "Answer": 33, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "4 + 5 * 1 =", "Answer": 9, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "0 + 3 * 7 =", "Answer": 21, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "8 + 5 * 0 =", "Answer": 8, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "4 + 6 * 5 =", "Answer": 34, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "5 + 4 * 5 =", "Answer": 25, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "0 + 2 * 6 =", "Answer": 12, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "3 + 5 * 6 =", "Answer": 33, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "7 + 3 * 2 =", "Answer": 13, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "5 + 7 * 1 =", "Answer": 12, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "4 + 4 * 1 =", "Answer": 8, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "4 + 8 * 3 =", "Answer": 28, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "0 + 0 * 4 =", "Answer": 0, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "0 + 6 * 2 =", "Answer": 12, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 3 * 5 =", "Answer": 17, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "5 + 8 * 4 =", "Answer": 37, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "4 + 3 * 9 =", "Answer": 31, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "1 + 3 * 5 =", "Answer": 16, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "4 + 4 * 4 =", "Answer": 20, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "5 + 0 * 2 =", "Answer": 5, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "4 + 5 * 6 =", "Answer": 34, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "0 + 5 * 4 =", "Answer": 20, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "6 + 2 * 0 =", "Answer": 6, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "8 + 1 * 5 =", "Answer": 13, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 8 * 2 =", "Answer": 25, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "8 + 2 * 6 =", "Answer": 20, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "8 + 8 * 9 =", "Answer": 80, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 3 * 6 =", "Answer": 20, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "8 + 4 * 4 =", "Answer": 24, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "8 + 3 * 6 =", "Answer": 26, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "1 + 0 * 5 =", "Answer": 1, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "0 + 9 * 7 =", "Answer": 63, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "1 + 1 * 1 =", "Answer": 2, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 0 * 5 =", "Answer": 9, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "8 + 7 * 2 =", "Answer": 22, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "3 + 1 * 4 =", "Answer": 7, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "1 + 0 * 2 =", "Answer": 1, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "7 + 6 * 8 =", "Answer": 55, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "8 + 8 * 3 =", "Answer": 32, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "7 + 5 * 7 =", "Answer": 42, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "4 + 1 * 8 =", "Answer": 12, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "7 + 7 * 9 =", "Answer": 70, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "7 + 2 * 1 =", "Answer": 9, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "9 + 6 * 4 =", "Answer": 33, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "8 + 3 * 7 =", "Answer": 29, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "5 + 7 * 3 =", "Answer": 26, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "5 + 9 * 8 =", "Answer": 77, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "3 + 4 * 7 =", "Answer": 31, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 6 * 0 =", "Answer": 2, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "1 + 2 * 8 =", "Answer": 17, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "3 + 1 * 8 =", "Answer": 11, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "5 + 3 * 5 =", "Answer": 20, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "6 + 4 * 3 =", "Answer": 18, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "7 + 4 * 2 =", "Answer": 15, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "1 + 0 * 6 =", "Answer": 1, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "7 + 1 * 2 =", "Answer": 9, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "7 + 7 * 2 =", "Answer": 21, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "6 + 6 * 0 =", "Answer": 6, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "7 + 9 * 0 =", "Answer": 7, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "3 + 7 * 9 =", "Answer": 66, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "3 + 4 * 0 =", "Answer": 3, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "5 + 1 * 2 =", "Answer": 7, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "6 + 1 * 6 =", "Answer": 12, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 1 * 5 =", "Answer": 7, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "4 + 6 * 7 =", "Answer": 46, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 4 * 9 =", "Answer": 38, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "2 + 7 * 7 =", "Answer": 51, "Type": "PM"}
{"Question": "6 * 7 + 9 =", "Answer": 51, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "0 * 4 + 8 =", "Answer": 8, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 4 + 6 =", "Answer": 18, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "8 * 7 + 8 =", "Answer": 64, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "6 * 9 + 2 =", "Answer": 56, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 5 + 9 =", "Answer": 14, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "5 * 1 + 5 =", "Answer": 10, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "6 * 2 + 4 =", "Answer": 16, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 4 + 1 =", "Answer": 13, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 5 + 1 =", "Answer": 36, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "4 * 7 + 2 =", "Answer": 30, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 4 + 6 =", "Answer": 10, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "5 * 0 + 8 =", "Answer": 8, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "0 * 4 + 3 =", "Answer": 3, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "4 * 7 + 8 =", "Answer": 36, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "8 * 1 + 2 =", "Answer": 10, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "2 * 6 + 3 =", "Answer": 15, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "0 * 2 + 0 =", "Answer": 0, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "8 * 1 + 1 =", "Answer": 9, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 2 + 6 =", "Answer": 20, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "0 * 7 + 9 =", "Answer": 9, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "0 * 5 + 2 =", "Answer": 2, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "5 * 4 + 9 =", "Answer": 29, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "0 * 9 + 6 =", "Answer": 6, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "4 * 0 + 3 =", "Answer": 3, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "2 * 6 + 6 =", "Answer": 18, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "5 * 1 + 1 =", "Answer": 6, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 4 + 9 =", "Answer": 13, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "2 * 0 + 7 =", "Answer": 7, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "6 * 4 + 6 =", "Answer": 30, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 2 + 7 =", "Answer": 13, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "8 * 0 + 4 =", "Answer": 4, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "5 * 8 + 0 =", "Answer": 40, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "9 * 0 + 4 =", "Answer": 4, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 5 + 4 =", "Answer": 9, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "2 * 8 + 5 =", "Answer": 21, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 2 + 9 =", "Answer": 11, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "6 * 8 + 7 =", "Answer": 55, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "0 * 1 + 3 =", "Answer": 3, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 9 + 3 =", "Answer": 12, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "0 * 1 + 5 =", "Answer": 5, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 1 + 0 =", "Answer": 1, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "4 * 7 + 5 =", "Answer": 33, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 2 + 7 =", "Answer": 21, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "9 * 6 + 9 =", "Answer": 63, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "6 * 2 + 7 =", "Answer": 19, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 7 + 4 =", "Answer": 53, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "5 * 5 + 5 =", "Answer": 30, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 0 + 5 =", "Answer": 5, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 5 + 3 =", "Answer": 8, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "8 * 8 + 7 =", "Answer": 71, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "6 * 6 + 3 =", "Answer": 39, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "4 * 7 + 6 =", "Answer": 34, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 8 + 7 =", "Answer": 31, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "4 * 9 + 1 =", "Answer": 37, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "8 * 5 + 6 =", "Answer": 46, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 3 + 7 =", "Answer": 10, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "6 * 5 + 9 =", "Answer": 39, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 2 + 2 =", "Answer": 8, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 8 + 9 =", "Answer": 33, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "8 * 2 + 5 =", "Answer": 21, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "2 * 1 + 2 =", "Answer": 4, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 6 + 0 =", "Answer": 42, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "4 * 3 + 7 =", "Answer": 19, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 3 + 6 =", "Answer": 27, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "4 * 1 + 9 =", "Answer": 13, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "5 * 3 + 9 =", "Answer": 24, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 6 + 3 =", "Answer": 21, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 8 + 9 =", "Answer": 65, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 1 + 4 =", "Answer": 5, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "6 * 7 + 1 =", "Answer": 43, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "2 * 3 + 9 =", "Answer": 15, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 9 + 6 =", "Answer": 33, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "0 * 9 + 3 =", "Answer": 3, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "2 * 6 + 9 =", "Answer": 21, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "2 * 7 + 5 =", "Answer": 19, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 8 + 2 =", "Answer": 26, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "5 * 7 + 0 =", "Answer": 35, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "2 * 4 + 4 =", "Answer": 12, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "8 * 4 + 6 =", "Answer": 38, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "0 * 0 + 3 =", "Answer": 3, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "6 * 5 + 6 =", "Answer": 36, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "6 * 1 + 8 =", "Answer": 14, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "5 * 2 + 7 =", "Answer": 17, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "9 * 0 + 3 =", "Answer": 3, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 6 + 2 =", "Answer": 20, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "5 * 4 + 1 =", "Answer": 21, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "2 * 5 + 9 =", "Answer": 19, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 6 + 7 =", "Answer": 49, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "4 * 6 + 3 =", "Answer": 27, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "9 * 8 + 5 =", "Answer": 77, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "6 * 4 + 1 =", "Answer": 25, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "4 * 1 + 0 =", "Answer": 4, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "8 * 8 + 1 =", "Answer": 65, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 7 + 7 =", "Answer": 56, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 3 + 2 =", "Answer": 11, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "6 * 8 + 1 =", "Answer": 49, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "8 * 4 + 8 =", "Answer": 40, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 0 + 0 =", "Answer": 0, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 0 + 5 =", "Answer": 5, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 4 + 5 =", "Answer": 17, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "9 * 5 + 8 =", "Answer": 53, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "9 * 2 + 6 =", "Answer": 24, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 7 + 6 =", "Answer": 27, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "9 * 2 + 5 =", "Answer": 23, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "4 * 6 + 2 =", "Answer": 26, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "8 * 0 + 1 =", "Answer": 1, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "9 * 2 + 1 =", "Answer": 19, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 8 + 5 =", "Answer": 61, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "2 * 9 + 4 =", "Answer": 22, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "9 * 2 + 7 =", "Answer": 25, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "0 * 6 + 9 =", "Answer": 9, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 2 + 3 =", "Answer": 5, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "0 * 4 + 6 =", "Answer": 6, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 7 + 7 =", "Answer": 28, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "9 * 7 + 5 =", "Answer": 68, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "4 * 0 + 2 =", "Answer": 2, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "5 * 1 + 8 =", "Answer": 13, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "2 * 9 + 8 =", "Answer": 26, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 9 + 9 =", "Answer": 18, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "0 * 3 + 3 =", "Answer": 3, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "8 * 6 + 4 =", "Answer": 52, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 7 + 8 =", "Answer": 29, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 2 + 6 =", "Answer": 12, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 6 + 4 =", "Answer": 22, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "0 * 3 + 4 =", "Answer": 4, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 0 + 0 =", "Answer": 0, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "4 * 9 + 0 =", "Answer": 36, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "5 * 1 + 6 =", "Answer": 11, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "0 * 6 + 0 =", "Answer": 0, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 9 + 2 =", "Answer": 65, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 5 + 3 =", "Answer": 18, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "6 * 1 + 7 =", "Answer": 13, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "8 * 2 + 4 =", "Answer": 20, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "2 * 4 + 2 =", "Answer": 10, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "6 * 4 + 8 =", "Answer": 32, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "5 * 8 + 3 =", "Answer": 43, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "8 * 0 + 7 =", "Answer": 7, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "8 * 9 + 9 =", "Answer": 81, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "6 * 0 + 9 =", "Answer": 9, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 4 + 7 =", "Answer": 11, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "8 * 0 + 5 =", "Answer": 5, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "6 * 6 + 7 =", "Answer": 43, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "4 * 7 + 9 =", "Answer": 37, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 5 + 7 =", "Answer": 12, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "0 * 4 + 2 =", "Answer": 2, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "5 * 1 + 7 =", "Answer": 12, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "8 * 6 + 9 =", "Answer": 57, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "4 * 4 + 7 =", "Answer": 23, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "9 * 7 + 0 =", "Answer": 63, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "2 * 9 + 5 =", "Answer": 23, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "0 * 6 + 7 =", "Answer": 7, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "6 * 8 + 4 =", "Answer": 52, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 3 + 3 =", "Answer": 12, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 7 + 5 =", "Answer": 12, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 8 + 0 =", "Answer": 56, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 4 + 9 =", "Answer": 21, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 0 + 9 =", "Answer": 9, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 0 + 3 =", "Answer": 3, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "9 * 8 + 9 =", "Answer": 81, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 1 + 7 =", "Answer": 10, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "5 * 0 + 0 =", "Answer": 0, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "9 * 6 + 8 =", "Answer": 62, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "9 * 0 + 6 =", "Answer": 6, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "4 * 2 + 8 =", "Answer": 16, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 4 + 8 =", "Answer": 36, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "9 * 8 + 7 =", "Answer": 79, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "8 * 4 + 5 =", "Answer": 37, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "6 * 5 + 4 =", "Answer": 34, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "4 * 6 + 9 =", "Answer": 33, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "6 * 5 + 1 =", "Answer": 31, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 1 + 6 =", "Answer": 7, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "0 * 4 + 1 =", "Answer": 1, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "6 * 7 + 8 =", "Answer": 50, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "8 * 6 + 8 =", "Answer": 56, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "6 * 0 + 3 =", "Answer": 3, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "2 * 5 + 2 =", "Answer": 12, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 1 + 9 =", "Answer": 12, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "9 * 2 + 0 =", "Answer": 18, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 2 + 4 =", "Answer": 18, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 9 + 5 =", "Answer": 68, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "4 * 3 + 4 =", "Answer": 16, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "5 * 5 + 1 =", "Answer": 26, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "8 * 9 + 5 =", "Answer": 77, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "4 * 2 + 9 =", "Answer": 17, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "6 * 9 + 0 =", "Answer": 54, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "6 * 5 + 2 =", "Answer": 32, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 3 + 4 =", "Answer": 25, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "2 * 9 + 2 =", "Answer": 20, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 3 + 1 =", "Answer": 22, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 8 + 8 =", "Answer": 16, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 1 + 2 =", "Answer": 5, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 5 + 5 =", "Answer": 40, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 0 + 7 =", "Answer": 7, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "8 * 1 + 7 =", "Answer": 15, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "2 * 5 + 5 =", "Answer": 15, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "2 * 5 + 3 =", "Answer": 13, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 8 + 1 =", "Answer": 25, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 1 + 5 =", "Answer": 8, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "4 * 7 + 0 =", "Answer": 28, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "0 * 8 + 7 =", "Answer": 7, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 9 + 1 =", "Answer": 28, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "6 * 3 + 3 =", "Answer": 21, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "8 * 3 + 8 =", "Answer": 32, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "4 * 5 + 2 =", "Answer": 22, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "8 * 2 + 1 =", "Answer": 17, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "5 * 1 + 3 =", "Answer": 8, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 9 + 5 =", "Answer": 14, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 1 + 4 =", "Answer": 11, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 6 + 8 =", "Answer": 26, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "0 * 4 + 5 =", "Answer": 5, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "8 * 0 + 9 =", "Answer": 9, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "2 * 9 + 6 =", "Answer": 24, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "8 * 2 + 9 =", "Answer": 25, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 4 + 1 =", "Answer": 29, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "4 * 4 + 8 =", "Answer": 24, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 5 + 8 =", "Answer": 23, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 6 + 3 =", "Answer": 45, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 0 + 4 =", "Answer": 4, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "0 * 9 + 8 =", "Answer": 8, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 0 + 4 =", "Answer": 4, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "0 * 9 + 5 =", "Answer": 5, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "6 * 9 + 6 =", "Answer": 60, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 2 + 3 =", "Answer": 17, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "2 * 4 + 1 =", "Answer": 9, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 1 + 7 =", "Answer": 14, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 5 + 6 =", "Answer": 41, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 7 + 1 =", "Answer": 8, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "0 * 5 + 1 =", "Answer": 1, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 1 + 5 =", "Answer": 12, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 9 + 7 =", "Answer": 34, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "5 * 2 + 9 =", "Answer": 19, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 7 + 7 =", "Answer": 14, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "8 * 8 + 0 =", "Answer": 64, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 9 + 3 =", "Answer": 30, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "9 * 8 + 0 =", "Answer": 72, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 0 + 8 =", "Answer": 8, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 5 + 0 =", "Answer": 5, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "6 * 1 + 3 =", "Answer": 9, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "9 * 5 + 4 =", "Answer": 49, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "0 * 2 + 1 =", "Answer": 1, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 6 + 1 =", "Answer": 43, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "0 * 8 + 8 =", "Answer": 8, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 1 + 8 =", "Answer": 9, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "0 * 0 + 9 =", "Answer": 9, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "6 * 9 + 7 =", "Answer": 61, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 2 + 9 =", "Answer": 23, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "0 * 3 + 5 =", "Answer": 5, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 7 + 4 =", "Answer": 11, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "5 * 3 + 6 =", "Answer": 21, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "2 * 6 + 1 =", "Answer": 13, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 8 + 5 =", "Answer": 13, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "2 * 7 + 1 =", "Answer": 15, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "5 * 4 + 7 =", "Answer": 27, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 9 + 8 =", "Answer": 35, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 2 + 2 =", "Answer": 4, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "0 * 6 + 8 =", "Answer": 8, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 9 + 3 =", "Answer": 66, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 3 + 8 =", "Answer": 17, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "4 * 5 + 7 =", "Answer": 27, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "8 * 1 + 4 =", "Answer": 12, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "0 * 9 + 0 =", "Answer": 0, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "4 * 0 + 4 =", "Answer": 4, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "4 * 1 + 5 =", "Answer": 9, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "5 * 7 + 6 =", "Answer": 41, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 6 + 0 =", "Answer": 18, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "9 * 9 + 6 =", "Answer": 87, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 4 + 5 =", "Answer": 9, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "2 * 2 + 6 =", "Answer": 10, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "6 * 9 + 5 =", "Answer": 59, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "6 * 1 + 9 =", "Answer": 15, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "6 * 8 + 0 =", "Answer": 48, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "8 * 4 + 0 =", "Answer": 32, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "0 * 6 + 1 =", "Answer": 1, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "5 * 0 + 4 =", "Answer": 4, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 3 + 5 =", "Answer": 26, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "9 * 5 + 2 =", "Answer": 47, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "2 * 0 + 8 =", "Answer": 8, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 8 + 2 =", "Answer": 58, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "9 * 1 + 9 =", "Answer": 18, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 0 + 6 =", "Answer": 6, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "8 * 9 + 6 =", "Answer": 78, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "0 * 7 + 4 =", "Answer": 4, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "9 * 3 + 7 =", "Answer": 34, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 6 + 6 =", "Answer": 48, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 3 + 9 =", "Answer": 30, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 2 + 9 =", "Answer": 15, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 4 + 2 =", "Answer": 6, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "3 * 2 + 0 =", "Answer": 6, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "0 * 8 + 5 =", "Answer": 5, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "7 * 4 + 6 =", "Answer": 34, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "6 * 9 + 1 =", "Answer": 55, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "9 * 1 + 0 =", "Answer": 9, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 0 + 7 =", "Answer": 7, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "1 * 8 + 3 =", "Answer": 11, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "6 * 8 + 8 =", "Answer": 56, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "8 * 4 + 9 =", "Answer": 41, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "4 * 3 + 8 =", "Answer": 20, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "2 * 0 + 1 =", "Answer": 1, "Type": "MP"}
{"Question": "4 * 4 + 5 =", "Answer": 21, "Type": "MP"}
